(Amy:)It's not surprising that
the story has captured
(Amy:)the attention of our
little circle of friends.
(Amy:)Are you familiar
with meme theory?
(Sheldon:)I'm familiar with
everything, but go on.
(Amy:)Meme theory suggests
(Amy:)that items of gossip
are like living things
(Amy:)that seek to reproduce
using humans as their host.
(Sheldon:)I'm no stranger to
memetic epidemiology.
(Sheldon:)At Johnson Elementary School,
the phrase "Shelly Cooper's
a smelly pooper" spread like wildfire.
(Amy:)I should think so.
(Amy:)That's gold.
(Sheldon:)Your meme hypothesis
does intrigue me.
(Sheldon:)How might we examine
this more closely?
(Amy:)Do you have any ethical qualms
regarding human experimentation?
(Sheldon:)It's one of the few forms of interaction
with people that I don't find repellent.
(Amy:)We need to fabricate a
tantalizing piece of gossip.
(Sheldon:)And a second non-tantalizing
piece to use as a control.